<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Info</title>
    <link href="https://info.rbnsn.uk/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://info.rbnsn.uk" />
    <updated>2023-08-15T21:09:05+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Joe Robinson</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://info.rbnsn.uk</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Available addresses</title>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Robinson</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://info.rbnsn.uk/available-addresses.html"/>
        <id>https://info.rbnsn.uk/available-addresses.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/3/available-ip-addresses-screenshot-2.jpg" medium="image" />
            <category term="Mac"/>
            <category term="Linux"/>

        <updated>2023-08-15T21:09:05+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/3/available-ip-addresses-screenshot-2.jpg" alt="" />
                    The scenario You want to add a new server/VM/container to your network and you want to statically assign the address. But, you don’t keep records of what is where and which IP addresses are assigned. I have been just copying and pasting in a bash&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/3/available-ip-addresses-screenshot-2.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                
    <h2 id="the-scenario">
      The scenario
    </h2>

  <p>
    You want to add a new server/VM/container to your network and you want to statically assign the address. But, you don’t keep records of what is where and which IP addresses are assigned.
  </p>

    <h2 id="the-workaroundlessbrgreater">
      The workaround<br>
    </h2>

  <p>
    I have been just copying and pasting in a bash script to get the results of what IP addresses are available. It works but it isn’t super.
  </p>
<pre class="line-numbers  language-bash"><code>for i in {1..254}; do ping -c 1 -W 100 192.168.100.$i | grep 'time='; done</code></pre>

    <h2 id="something-a-bit-betterlessbrgreater">
      Something a bit better<br>
    </h2>

  <p>
    I am usually working from my laptop when I am looking for a spare address within a range. So, I figured I could use a bash script that can be kept in the home directory and when it is run it will accept some a start and an end address. It takes those arguments and checks all of the IP addresses within. There is also some colouring to make it a bit more obvious which addresses are free and which are in use.<br><br>You will need to have nmap installed on your system/server for the script to work<br>
  </p>
<pre class="line-numbers  language-bash"><code>#!/bin/bash
# ANSI color codes
# Green background and black text for available IP addresses
GREEN_BG='\033[42;30m'
# Red background for in-use IP addresses
RED_BG='\033[41m'
# No color (reset)
NC='\033[0m'
# Function to check if an IP address is reachable
check_ip() {
    local ip=$1
    if ping -c 1 -W 1 "$ip" &&gt;/dev/null; then
        echo -e "${RED_BG} $ip is in use. ${NC}"
    else
        echo -e "${GREEN_BG} $ip is available. ${NC}"
    fi
}
# Input range in the format:  
read -p "Enter the starting IP address: " start_ip
read -p "Enter the ending IP address: " end_ip
# Extract the prefix from the starting IP address
prefix=$(echo "$start_ip" | cut -d '.' -f 1-3)
# Loop through the IP range and check availability
for ((i = $(echo "${start_ip}" | cut -d '.' -f 4); i &lt;= $(echo "${end_ip}" | cut -d '.' -f 4); i++)); do
    ip_address="${prefix}.${i}"
    check_ip "$ip_address"
done
chmod +x ping_range.sh
</code></pre>

  <p>
    Then you run it<br>
  </p>
<pre class="line-numbers  language-bash"><code>./ping_range.sh
</code></pre>

  <p>
    What it looks like
  </p>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--wide">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/3/SCR-20230731-nfrv-2.png" height="427" width="776" alt=""  sizes="100vw" srcset="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/3/responsive/SCR-20230731-nfrv-2-xs.png 300w ,https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/3/responsive/SCR-20230731-nfrv-2-sm.png 480w ,https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/3/responsive/SCR-20230731-nfrv-2-md.png 768w ,https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/3/responsive/SCR-20230731-nfrv-2-lg.png 1024w ,https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/3/responsive/SCR-20230731-nfrv-2-xl.png 1360w ,https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/3/responsive/SCR-20230731-nfrv-2-2xl.png 1600w">
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    You will quickly see which IPs are available and which aren’t
  </p>

  <p>
    It is pretty obvious which addresses are available for use 👍
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Block post</title>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Robinson</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://info.rbnsn.uk/block-post.html"/>
        <id>https://info.rbnsn.uk/block-post.html</id>

        <updated>2023-08-14T21:19:54+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    This is a second level heading This a third level heading
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
    <figure class="post__image post__image--full">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/2/lagoon-nebula-11143-1.jpg" height="200" width="1200" alt=""  sizes="100vw" srcset="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/2/responsive/lagoon-nebula-11143-1-xs.jpg 300w ,https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/2/responsive/lagoon-nebula-11143-1-sm.jpg 480w ,https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/2/responsive/lagoon-nebula-11143-1-md.jpg 768w ,https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/2/responsive/lagoon-nebula-11143-1-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/2/responsive/lagoon-nebula-11143-1-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/2/responsive/lagoon-nebula-11143-1-2xl.jpg 1600w">
      
    </figure>

    <h2 id="this-is-a-second-level-heading">
      This is a second level heading
    </h2>

    <h3 id="this-a-third-level-heading">
      This a third level heading
    </h3>

  <p>
    
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Test post</title>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Robinson</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://info.rbnsn.uk/test-post.html"/>
        <id>https://info.rbnsn.uk/test-post.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/1/available-ip-addresses-screenshot.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2023-08-15T19:53:44+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/1/available-ip-addresses-screenshot.jpg" alt="" />
                    As always, it is fillerama content Who’s that then? I am your king. Shut up! Will you shut up?! Why? The swallow may fly south with the sun, and the house martin or the plover may seek warmer climes in winter, yet these are not&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/1/available-ip-addresses-screenshot.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <blockquote>
<p>As always, it is fillerama content</p>
</blockquote>
<h1 id="well-howd-you-become-king-then">Well, how’d you become king, then?</h1>
<p>Who’s that then? I am your king. Shut up! Will you shut up?! Why?</p>
<p>The swallow may fly south with the sun, and the house martin or the plover may seek warmer climes in winter, yet these are not strangers to our land. <strong>…Are you suggesting that coconuts migrate?</strong> <em>And the hat.</em> She’s a witch!</p>
<h2 id="the-nose">The nose?</h2>
<p>She looks like one. Be quiet! And the hat. She’s a witch! Burn her! Look, my liege!</p>
<ol>
<li>I don’t want to talk to you no more, you empty-headed animal food trough water! I fart in your general direction! Your mother was a hamster and your father smelt of elderberries! Now leave before I am forced to taunt you a second time!</li>
<li>Well, she turned me into a newt.</li>
<li>A newt?</li>
</ol>
<h3 id="did-you-dress-her-up-like-this">Did you dress her up like this?</h3>
<p>Found them? In Mercia?! The coconut’s tropical! Burn her anyway! You can’t expect to wield supreme power just ‘cause some watery tart threw a sword at you! But you are dressed as one… Found them? In Mercia?! The coconut’s tropical!</p>
<ul>
<li>It’s only a model.</li>
<li>Ah, now we see the violence inherent in the system!</li>
<li>Well, Mercia’s a temperate zone!</li>
</ul>
<p>Found them? In Mercia?! The coconut’s tropical! Why do you think that she is a witch? We found them. I have to push the pram a lot. A newt? What a strange person.</p>
<p>Well, we did do the nose. Be quiet! I have to push the pram a lot. Well, we did do the nose.</p>
<p>Shut up! Will you shut up?! I dunno. Must be a king. It’s only a model. You can’t expect to wield supreme power just ‘cause some watery tart threw a sword at you! What a strange person.</p>
<p>I’m not a witch. I don’t want to talk to you no more, you empty-headed animal food trough water! I fart in your general direction! Your mother was a hamster and your father smelt of elderberries! Now leave before I am forced to taunt you a second time!</p>
<p>Shh! Knights, I bid you welcome to your new home. Let us ride to Camelot! But you are dressed as one… Well, what do you want? Ah, now we see the violence inherent in the system! Found them? In Mercia?! The coconut’s tropical!</p>
<p>Ah, now we see the violence inherent in the system! Well, I got better. You can’t expect to wield supreme power just ‘cause some watery tart threw a sword at you! Ni! Ni! Ni! Ni! Be quiet! Why do you think that she is a witch?</p>
<p>What a strange person. Listen. Strange women lying in ponds distributing swords is no basis for a system of government. Supreme executive power derives from a mandate from the masses, not from some farcical aquatic ceremony.</p>
<p>Well, what do you want? But you are dressed as one… The swallow may fly south with the sun, and the house martin or the plover may seek warmer climes in winter, yet these are not strangers to our land.</p>
<p>Shh! Knights, I bid you welcome to your new home. Let us ride to Camelot! How do you know she is a witch? Listen. Strange women lying in ponds distributing swords is no basis for a system of government. Supreme executive power derives from a mandate from the masses, not from some farcical aquatic ceremony.</p>
<p>Oh, ow! The Lady of the Lake, her arm clad in the purest shimmering samite, held aloft Excalibur from the bosom of the water, signifying by divine providence that I, Arthur, was to carry Excalibur. That is why I am your king.</p>
<p>Well, I got better. Why do you think that she is a witch? I dunno. Must be a king. What a strange person. How do you know she is a witch?</p>
<h2 id="second-level">Second level</h2>
<h3 id="third-level">Third level</h3>
<h4 id="this-belongs-to-the-third-level">This belongs to the third level</h4>
<h4 id="so-does-this-one">So does this one</h4>
<h3 id="another-third-level-heading">another third level heading.</h3>
<p>Is it all added to the table of contents?</p>
<h4 id="it-is-that-is-nice">It is, that is nice</h4>
<p>And now for something completely different.</p>
<pre><code class="language-python">import os

def which_os(self)
    print(os.info)
</code></pre>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
