<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Info</title>
    <link href="https://info.rbnsn.uk/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://info.rbnsn.uk" />
    <updated>2023-08-14T21:11:55+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Joe Robinson</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://info.rbnsn.uk</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Test post</title>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Robinson</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://info.rbnsn.uk/test-post.html"/>
        <id>https://info.rbnsn.uk/test-post.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/1/available-ip-addresses-screenshot.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2023-08-14T21:11:55+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/1/available-ip-addresses-screenshot.jpg" alt="" />
                    As always, it is fillerama content Who’s that then? I am your king. Shut up! Will you shut up?! Why? The swallow may fly south&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://info.rbnsn.uk/media/posts/1/available-ip-addresses-screenshot.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <blockquote>
<p>As always, it is fillerama content</p>
</blockquote>
<h1 id="well-howd-you-become-king-then">Well, how’d you become king, then?</h1>
<p>Who’s that then? I am your king. Shut up! Will you shut up?! Why?</p>
<p>The swallow may fly south with the sun, and the house martin or the plover may seek warmer climes in winter, yet these are not strangers to our land. <strong>…Are you suggesting that coconuts migrate?</strong> <em>And the hat.</em> She’s a witch!</p>
<h2 id="the-nose">The nose?</h2>
<p>She looks like one. Be quiet! And the hat. She’s a witch! Burn her! Look, my liege!</p>
<ol>
<li>I don’t want to talk to you no more, you empty-headed animal food trough water! I fart in your general direction! Your mother was a hamster and your father smelt of elderberries! Now leave before I am forced to taunt you a second time!</li>
<li>Well, she turned me into a newt.</li>
<li>A newt?</li>
</ol>
<h3 id="did-you-dress-her-up-like-this">Did you dress her up like this?</h3>
<p>Found them? In Mercia?! The coconut’s tropical! Burn her anyway! You can’t expect to wield supreme power just ‘cause some watery tart threw a sword at you! But you are dressed as one… Found them? In Mercia?! The coconut’s tropical!</p>
<ul>
<li>It’s only a model.</li>
<li>Ah, now we see the violence inherent in the system!</li>
<li>Well, Mercia’s a temperate zone!</li>
</ul>
<p>Found them? In Mercia?! The coconut’s tropical! Why do you think that she is a witch? We found them. I have to push the pram a lot. A newt? What a strange person.</p>
<p>Well, we did do the nose. Be quiet! I have to push the pram a lot. Well, we did do the nose.</p>
<p>Shut up! Will you shut up?! I dunno. Must be a king. It’s only a model. You can’t expect to wield supreme power just ‘cause some watery tart threw a sword at you! What a strange person.</p>
<p>I’m not a witch. I don’t want to talk to you no more, you empty-headed animal food trough water! I fart in your general direction! Your mother was a hamster and your father smelt of elderberries! Now leave before I am forced to taunt you a second time!</p>
<p>Shh! Knights, I bid you welcome to your new home. Let us ride to Camelot! But you are dressed as one… Well, what do you want? Ah, now we see the violence inherent in the system! Found them? In Mercia?! The coconut’s tropical!</p>
<p>Ah, now we see the violence inherent in the system! Well, I got better. You can’t expect to wield supreme power just ‘cause some watery tart threw a sword at you! Ni! Ni! Ni! Ni! Be quiet! Why do you think that she is a witch?</p>
<p>What a strange person. Listen. Strange women lying in ponds distributing swords is no basis for a system of government. Supreme executive power derives from a mandate from the masses, not from some farcical aquatic ceremony.</p>
<p>Well, what do you want? But you are dressed as one… The swallow may fly south with the sun, and the house martin or the plover may seek warmer climes in winter, yet these are not strangers to our land.</p>
<p>Shh! Knights, I bid you welcome to your new home. Let us ride to Camelot! How do you know she is a witch? Listen. Strange women lying in ponds distributing swords is no basis for a system of government. Supreme executive power derives from a mandate from the masses, not from some farcical aquatic ceremony.</p>
<p>Oh, ow! The Lady of the Lake, her arm clad in the purest shimmering samite, held aloft Excalibur from the bosom of the water, signifying by divine providence that I, Arthur, was to carry Excalibur. That is why I am your king.</p>
<p>Well, I got better. Why do you think that she is a witch? I dunno. Must be a king. What a strange person. How do you know she is a witch?</p>
<h2 id="second-level">Second level</h2>
<h3 id="third-level">Third level</h3>
<h4 id="this-belongs-to-the-third-level">This belongs to the third level</h4>
<h4 id="so-does-this-one">So does this one</h4>
<h3 id="another-third-level-heading-is-it-all-added-to-the-table-of-contents">another third level heading. Is it all added to the table of contents?</h3>
<h4 id="it-is-that-is-nice">It is, that is nice</h4>
<pre><code class="language-python">import os

def which_os(self)
    print(os.info)
</code></pre>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
